<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
<name>[KV] Animal Costumes - B19</name>
<author>Kiame</author>
<targetVersion>0.19.0</targetVersion>
<description>Just in time for Halloween: Animal Costumes!

Included are Ears, Tails, and Hooded Costumes of Tanooki, Cats, and Dogs.

Each accessory/costume imbues the wearer with aspects of the animal.
The Tanooki is sly and wise - bonuses to work-related tasks like research, growing, crafting and negative combat stats.
The cat is agile a fierce - bonus to melee combat and negative ranged comabt.
The dog is loyal and ready to retrieve the kill (still working on this description...) - bonus to ranged combat and negative melee combat.

The tails and ears give small bonuses - 1% in most cases - whereas the costume and hood give larger bonuses - 5% in most cases.

4 new research tasks.
-Animal Tails and Ears: Requires Complex Clothing. Allows crafting of Tanooki Ears and Tails.
-Combat Animal Tails and Ears: Requires Machining and Animal Tails and Ears. Allows crafting of Cat/Dog Ears and Tails - these have roughly the same armor as plate helm and plate armor with the addition of small stat bonuses.
-Animal Costumes: Requires Animal Tails and Ears and Microelectronics. Allows crafting of Tanooki Costume and Hood.
-Combat Animal Costumes: Requires Animal Costumes, Combat Animal Tails and Ears, and Powered Armor. Allows crafting of Cat/Dog Ears and Tails - these have roughly the same armor as power helm and power armor with the addition of stat bonuses.

For Cat/Dog armor, cat armor has equal protection from blunt and sharp whereas dog armor has higher sharp protection and lower blunt. In all cases the sum of the two (sharp+blunt) are the same between cat, dog, and the armor which they are comparable to (armored helm/chest or power helm/armor)

Make sure to farm cotton as these do require large amounts of leather/cotton to make.

Undergarment - unlocked with "Animal Costumes" research - is apparel with the slightly better protection than a t-shirt (it covers both shirt and legs). This was added to get more freedom with color combinations. Consider using Change Dresser - http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1135400593 - for custom colorations.

AI Raiders from Tribal and Outlander groups will uses these.

Do not use with Animal Ears - http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1101938667. Please disable that mod prior to loading this one.

P.S. Yes the actual name of the animal is Tanuki (not Tanooki) which is a japanese raccoon dog. This is homage to SMB3.</description>
</ModMetaData>